let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1.,
        question: 'Locus of |z|>1 is: ',
        answer: 'C. x2 + y2 < 1 ',
        options: [
            'A. x2 + y2 = 1',
            'B. x2 + y2 > 1',
            'C. x2 + y2 < 1',
            'D. x2 + y2 >= 1'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 2.,
        question: 'Argument of (z-1/z+1) is equal to',
        answer: 'A. tan-1 (2y/x2 +y2 -1)',
        options: [
            'A. tan-1 (2y/x2 +y2 -1)',
            'B. tan-1 (2x/x2+y2 -1)',
            'C. tan(2y/x2+y2-1)',
            'D. none of the above'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3.,
        question: 'if z=3+4i , then modulus of z is',
        answer: 'A. 5',
        options: [
            'A. 5',
            'B. 7',
            'C. 25',
            'D. 34'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4.,
        question: 'If f(z)=log z , then real of f(z) is',
        answer: 'A. log|z|',
        options: [
            'A. log|z|',
            'B. |z|',
            'C. theta',
            'D. r'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5.,
        question: 'Particular integral of ODE(D2 +1)Y=e+2x',
        answer: 'A. 1/5 ex',
        options: [
            'A. 1/5 ex',
            'B. 1/4 e2x',
            'C. 1/5 e2x',
            'D. 1/5'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6.,
        question: 'if f(x)=sin x is periodic function , then period of f(x) is',
        answer: 'C. 2π',
        options: [
            'A. π',
            'B. -π ',
            'C. 2π',
            'D. π/2'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7.,
        question: 'degree of ODE log(d2y/dx2)=5x is',
        answer: 'D. None',
        options: [
            'A. 2',
            'B. 3',
            'C. 0',
            'D. None'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8.,
        question: 'ODE dy/dx +Py=Qyn is linear if',
        answer: 'D. n=0',
        options: [
            'A. n=1',
            'B. n=2',
            'C. n=3',
            'D. n=0'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9.,
        question: 'Conjugate of complex number z=-3+i is',
        answer: 'A. -3-i',
        options: [
            'A. -3-i',
            'B. 3-i',
            'C. -3+i',
            'D. 3+i'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10.,
        question: 'roots of z4=1 are',
        answer: 'B. 1,-1,i,-i',
        options: [
            'A. 1,1,i,i',
            'B. 1,-1,i,-i',
            'C. i,i,i,i',
            'D. 1,1,1,1'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11.,
        question: 'amplitude of z=5/12i is ',
        answer: 'B. π/2',
        options: [
            'A. π/4',
            'B. π/2',
            'C. -π/2',
            'D. -π/4'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 12.,
        question: 'divergence of a vector point function is ',
        answer: 'A. Scalar',
        options: [
            'A. Scalar',
            'B. Vector',
            'C. both (A) and (B)',
            'D. none of the above'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13.,
        question: 'Roots of equation z2+1=0',
        answer: 'A. i ,-i',
        options: [
            'A. i ,-i',
            'B. 1,i',
            'C. 1,-1',
            'D. -1,i'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 14.,
        question: 'Real part of f(z)=4+I is',
        answer: 'B. 4',
        options: [
            'A. 1',
            'B. 4',
            'C. 4+i',
            'D. i'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15.,
        question: ' In fourier series of f(x) , coffecients a0,an, bn ',
        answer: 'B. fourier coefficients',
        options: [
            'A. laplace coefficients',
            'B. fourier coefficients',
            'C. taylors coefficients',
            'D. None'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 16.,
        question: 'Argument value of z=1+i is ',
        answer: 'B. π/4',
        options: [
            'A. π/2',
            'B. π/4',
            'C. 0',
            'D. -π/4'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17.,
        question: 'if (x+5)+i(y+3)=0',
        answer: 'D. x=-5,y=-3',
        options: [
            'A. x=5,y=3',
            'B. x=-5,y=3',
            'C. x=5,y=-3',
            'D. x=-5,y=-3'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 18.,
        question: 'if f(x)=sinxcos2x then f(x) is',
        answer: 'B. Odd function',
        options: [
            'A. Even function',
            'B. Odd function',
            'C. Neither even or odd',
            'D. NOT'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19.,
        question: 'If f(x)=cos x is defined in [-1,1] then fourier coefficient bn is',
        answer: 'D. 0',
        options: [
            'A. 4',
            'B. -1',
            'C. 1',
            'D. 0'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 20.,
        question: 'Real part of f(z)=sin z is',
        answer: 'B. sin x cos hy',
        options: [
            'A. sin x cos y',
            'B. sin x cos hy',
            'C. sin hx cos y',
            'D. sin x sin hy'
        ]
    }

]
